

DANIEL SANCHEZ VELANDIA



Frontend Developer

PERFIL

I'm a professional front-end developer with **3 years of experience** building fantastic UX experiences with good design core fundamentals. My focus is to combine creative thinking and design with an analytical approach to solve problems at the intersection of business and technology. I work great in teams and can be counted on to consistently deliver products above expectations.

Languages





ESPAÑOL 📠



Skills

JavaScript	JS
CSS —	=
HTML —	HTML
ReactJS —	
SASS	8
C# —	(3)
Python —	÷
Django —————	d
NodeJS	nede
MySQL —	En S
Postgres —	M
MongoDB —	•
Git/GitHub —	O
Docker —	-
Kubernetes —	₩
Bash ————	2
Blender —	₹

EDUCACION

Tecnologia en Sistemas

Leon de Greiff

2017

Santiago de Cali, Colombia

Ingenieria en Sistemas

Universidad del Valle

2019 - 2023

O Santiago de Cali, Colombia

EXPERIENCE

FullStack Developer

6/2019 - 3/2021 🛇 Santiago de Cali, Colombia

Alicante S.A.S

- Led the development of the company's landing page with Javascript-HTML-CSS-Webpack.
- Develop the database to register orders, receipts and clients.
- Worked with: Javascript, PHP, MySQL, Postman, C#.

FullStack Developer

9/2021 - 9/2022 🛇 Santiago de Cali, Colombia

Compuservix

- modernizing the desktop software to manage educational institutions to 100% web application. Using React C# .NET with Entity framework and Microsoft SQL Server as data management..
- Worked with: ReactJs, NodeJS, Material UI, WebSockets, C#, .NET.

CONTACT

- **\(+57-318-633-1339**
- @ danielsanchezvel@hotmail.com.com
- Santiago de Cali, Colombia

REFERENCES

Guillermo Yordan

CE0

@ gerencia_alicante@gmail.com

+57-318-780-6625

Samuel Espinoza

PROJECT MANAGER

info@samuelvelandia.com

& +57-317-502-5705